{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"9ebc1f9e-fa9f-4a31-9e40-aab120c044f0"},"exam":{"id":"de6a5321-03a2-466a-b34a-da3f1ee02a8f","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"00f56002-e145-4ed1-94f4-c041d0edd78f","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is a correct S3 bucket name?","explanation":"Bucket names must start with a lowercase letter or number and must not contain uppercase characters or underscores. 2nd-headquarters-imgs is the only bucket name listed here that adheres to these rules and restrictions.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"50ccd1e352082b9d31184e260c3830ef","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Second-headquarters-imgs","correct":false},{"id":"5457bb8e9a20209e28f939482cbf590c","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Headquartersimg","correct":false},{"id":"2b56c4f3ee0c03e44e37656e651fafcf","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd-headquarters-imgs","correct":true},{"id":"5d54f4723cb2118e1da2a67a7628f77d","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd_Headquarters_imgs","correct":false}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false}]},{"id":"cckhl0ep-pmhf-g8be-yplb-dzr17jgnk6mn","domain":"security","question":"Where is the best place to store your Root User Access Key so that your application can use it to make requests to AWS?","explanation":"It is not recommended to use Root User account or access keys for any reason as these grant full unrestricted access to the entire account. Recommended practice is to follow the concept of \"Least Privilege\" and create am IAM user or role with just enough access to do what is needed and nothing more, and use those keys as required","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-access-keys-best-practices.html","title":"Best Practices for Managing AWS Access Keys"}],"answers":[{"id":"503d72b0254a8561511b71a95f8eb8a7","text":"It should be configured as a parameter and held in the Key Management Store (KMS)","correct":false},{"id":"73532a5c24d7b4c1df276690bbaedfff","text":"In the .aws file in you application","correct":false},{"id":"9feb4a526584eae16c38880b7813f48c","text":"It needs to be coded directly into your application","correct":false},{"id":"2330278fe444dd9a6196cb146c97de7e","text":"Nowhere - you should not use the Root User access keys for this","correct":true}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"cliqnjyx-pd1z-74c0-p0h5-gl8ufv76fo42","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are valid EC2 pricing options?","explanation":"On-Demand, where you pay for the resources you have used at the end of the billing period, and Reserved, were you commit to paying a certain amount every billing period for a length of time no matter if you used them or not, are the valid EC2 pricing options.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"4cc6684df7b4a92b1dec6fce3264fac8","text":"Global","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isn’t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing – Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false},{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"01355a86-1c9a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"In Amazon EC2, which of the following do you use to log into Linux instances?","explanation":"To log into Linux instances using EC2, you will need a key pair; Windows instances are the ones that need a user name and password to log in. Multi-factor authentication (MFA) involves the addition of an extra layer of protection, such as a code generated from an authenticator, to a user name and password. MFA can be enabled to use with IAM, or Identity and Access Management.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_security-outside-iam.html","title":"Security Features Outside of IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":false},{"id":"1a504cebc3822fd967eb6426a7ff0a31","text":"Multi-factor authentication","correct":false},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"6cd56a4cc4ddbbfd2bc9d57de5d788aa","text":"Key pair","correct":true}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false},{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false}]},{"id":"og6hjhzz-5hd0-yz2y-lhcp-id573kosdzz0","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authentication\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authentication is the first part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":false},{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":true}]},{"id":"9a62e30f-6366-4ba3-a6f9-29118a4432d8","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the Reserved Instance pricing model?","explanation":"Reserved instances are a great way of reducing costs on long running applications with predictable workloads. Even if the money is not available to make upfront payments, using Reserved Instances over longer periods can still be useful for cost savings","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e757909a259f51f248d287636899abda","text":"Ability to bid on the lowest compute price possible","correct":false},{"id":"79c233b246a21fbcf2c865dcef7f0791","text":"Predictable workload types","correct":true},{"id":"642a643c75d27712431a1b79c28e8cc5","text":"Unpredictable workloads","correct":false},{"id":"f5bfd0de9a22ee48b87ae246ed4f4042","text":"CAPEX vs OPEX charging model","correct":true}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"pjzmsz8b-2lx2-8zb8-wauh-od1x4h0ja4pd","domain":"tech","question":"A new System Administrator has started with your organisation and requires a user account so that they can manage you AWS resources. You have AWS resources in multiple regions - what needs to be done to allow the new starter access to manage resources in the regions you operate in?","explanation":"Any answer that suggest a role is incorrect as roles by themselves will not let a user log in. The correct approach is to create an IAM user - and as IAM is a global service - configuration in IAM applies globally, not just regionally, only a single IAM user account is required.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"What is IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"98cddae0b6f5dfe1792d38678a9851a0","text":"Create an IAM role in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"2effe9ac093a8dcafdd02f3e97c1244e","text":"Create a single IAM role - this will enable access in all regions","correct":false},{"id":"f854b98dd0b3ff05864e11c45979706b","text":"Create a single IAM user account - this will enable access in all regions","correct":true},{"id":"15ed84de219d4333fe7069904bec4dbc","text":"Create an IAM user account in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"a392d2dd-28e1-4e5d-8a64-6a84e5e3f3e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which Elastic Load Balancer type would be best suited to help you host a website?","explanation":"Although it looks like the right answer - there is no \"Web\" load balancer in AWS. Instead, the Application Load Balancer fills this need. It is not recommended to use Classic Load Balancers anymore are these have been superseded, and a network Load Balancer is not right for this case.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","title":"Elastic Load Balancing"}],"answers":[{"id":"d35b51b639528d580362ca7042de6a0e","text":"Classic","correct":false},{"id":"c6e190b284633c48e39e55049da3cce8","text":"Web","correct":false},{"id":"e498749f3c42246d50b15c81c101d988","text":"Application","correct":true},{"id":"eec89088ee408b80387155272b113256","text":"Network","correct":false}]},{"id":"83246738-477a-40c5-8224-59d739ad6600","domain":"tech","question":"You are a solutions architect working for a New York-based digital marketing company specializing in local SEO. You are tasked with creating an S3 bucket to operate within the US West (N. California) Region. The company wants to name it with the IP address of the SEO Health Checker application that was recently developed for potential clients based in California to get a free website analysis report. Which of these actions would be most appropriate?","explanation":"Bucket names must not be formatted as an IP address. Indeed, each bucket name should be unique across all existing names in Amazon S3. So, following AWS naming rules, name the bucket after the type of data it will store.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"dc1cf44cc05f915cfa69e23237b4e6c0","text":"Simply name the bucket after the Region.","correct":false},{"id":"73d20a8bf6fd3ae4e325f0aba2e8a8c6","text":"Use dashes instead of periods in the IP address to comply with bucket naming rules.","correct":false},{"id":"49336715d3a6034152315aaa72ba1ca2","text":"That shouldn’t be a problem; name the bucket after the web application’s IP address.","correct":false},{"id":"557ad9f77b4777473a400e65c0bc146a","text":"Do not name the bucket after the application’s IP address.","correct":true}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"dln2owy5-ju7b-em4o-t3bo-ry23tbt3vrfy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes Availability Zones?","explanation":"Availability Zones are distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures. Each Region is made up of one or more AZs. Availability Zones host almost every AWS service, including EC2 instances, S3 buckets, and much more. Some services will maintain copies of your data between Availability Zones, but this is dependent on the individual service (for example, S3 can store data in multiple AZ's, where an EC2 instance is tied to a single AZ). AWS's Content Distribution Network (CDN) is known as CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c6c3ae50e5264fd89c1ea0bb3c10e963","text":"Restricted areas designed specifically for the creation of Virtual Private Clouds.","correct":false},{"id":"172cd3aac7dce24131bdafec9988a618","text":"A Content Distribution Network used to deliver content to users","correct":false},{"id":"5c9e81d4612f9e8cb24d82a6015586c5","text":"Distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures.","correct":true},{"id":"5b3edf7c62ba2925e93886b2fed63697","text":"Two zones containing compute resources that are designed to automatically maintain synchronized copies of each other's data.","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false},{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false},{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ayciun1-a7hg-i7yq-4oeq-elwlon69tcex","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below terms represents a series of Edge Locations plus information about how you want content managed as part of a CDN?","explanation":"A Distribution is made up of Edge Locations that you want to serve content from, and details about how that content will be tracked an managed. Edge Groups and Circulations are not CloudFront Concepts, and although Load Balancer is an AWS service that helps you direct web traffic, it is not applicable in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/distribution-working-with.html","title":"Working with Distributions"}],"answers":[{"id":"c680109c8813a5a660a981f781dc0b1e","text":"A Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"59e3676a32b06a177d0617fde3d2ca48","text":"An Edge Group","correct":false},{"id":"da8c85132b9bd45b3e8415405c753343","text":"A Circulation","correct":false},{"id":"4e4e3ccc157ce52c9ddcf1d7277faf6e","text":"A Distribution","correct":true}]},{"id":"84d8ac20-2fb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Once you exceed a usage percentage of Free Tier limits for any service, AWS will automatically send you an email notification. What is that percentage?","explanation":"If you exceed 85% of Free Tier usage, AWS will automatically send you an email to notify you. This is to alert you to help with staying within the Free Tier limits; otherwise, you may incur charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"c0c7c76d30bd3dcaefc96f40275bdc0a","text":"50","correct":false},{"id":"1c383cd30b7c298ab50293adfecb7b18","text":"35","correct":false},{"id":"d09bf41544a3365a46c9077ebb5e35c3","text":"75","correct":false},{"id":"3ef815416f775098fe977004015c6193","text":"85","correct":true}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false},{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"wvxqbzjc-c9jk-sld7-d5mu-q6zpjrfydg47","domain":"tech","question":"You have just created a new bucket and uploaded a file into it - will this be automatically viewable by anyone on the internet?","explanation":"By default, all data stored in S3 is NOT viewable by the public. If you want a bucket or object to be accessible by the public, you must explicitly make it so. NAT Gateways and Internet Gateways are needed to allow communications between VPCs and the internet, but are not required when it comes to S3","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/#security","title":"S3 Security"}],"answers":[{"id":"7b30b72e7721523c1467f2387b5fa089","text":"Yes - by default buckets and their contents are public","correct":false},{"id":"7e6adeafa366013b86b4a4bea96c16ef","text":"Only if you have an Internet Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"a8500b13e7e4474d341e354692b3af26","text":"Only if you have a NAT Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"c206c641ffd27b5062ee0b0d61cac9a5","text":"No - by default buckets and their contents are private","correct":true}]},{"id":"a1113592-8add-4bc5-bc72-07b4af069ecb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following enables customers to find, test, and buy software from independent vendors to run on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Marketplace is the place to get software that runs on AWS. Amazon Connect is a cloud-based contact center; AWS Cost Explorer is for evaluating your account costs and usage, and AWS Budgets is for budgeting costs and usage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace","title":"AWS Marketplace"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"cab27dc53edb571cac663ce2e16450dc","text":"AWS Marketplace","correct":true},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"3597dfc4f30310d82a68c84b2c82e1a8","text":"Amazon Connect","correct":false}]},{"id":"bfoxiudd-ep8s-9jah-t2ho-96nct3a3mjfh","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following data archival services is extremely inexpensive, but can have a multi-hour data-retrieval window?","explanation":"Glacier offers extremely inexpensive data archival, but requires a 3-5 hour data-retrieval window for standard retrievals - though this time can be reduced for a price. Other S3 storage tiers, including Infrequent Access (S3-IA) can all be accessed immediately, but some may incur additional fees for accessing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/?nc=sn&loc=3","title":"S3 Storage Classes"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"e9a5105fa288ef2b71c037e42d665d91","text":"S3 - OneZone-IA","correct":false},{"id":"31e831ec49678aed7f467f791d1f8704","text":"S3 - RRS","correct":false},{"id":"4340570ba672bfa48cd45e3f026c01d1","text":"S3 - IA","correct":false}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true}]},{"id":"150e71c2-9b46-4a48-bed4-ef89f73570ae","domain":"tech","question":"Although you know that your Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes are designed to be highly reliable, you want to further mitigate the possibility of a failure. Which of the following should you do?","explanation":"Backup of the EBS volumes can be created by taking point-in-time snapshots. These components are stored in S3. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/EBSSnapshots.html","title":"Amazon EBS Snapshots"},{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-building-fault-tolerant-applications.pdf?did=wp_card&trk=wp_card","title":"Fault-Tolerant Components on AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2f843acc6781a153857118f92da89f4","text":"Mitigating the possibility of a failure is not necessary.","correct":false},{"id":"2f63e74501f200b9859c7b5976101e79","text":"Make copies of the EBS volumes and store them in Amazon S3.","correct":false},{"id":"44023459578ef9dc57780fc55ee56f7d","text":"Take snapshots of the EBS volumes.","correct":true},{"id":"a2a7a68497095df080fb01033b2aea46","text":"Create backups of the EBS volumes in Amazon RDS.","correct":false}]},{"id":"4kl8vift-ulhd-37ni-39eb-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below can you host on S3?","explanation":"S3 can be used to host simple static websites - other types that are dynamic or require code to run on the server side cannot be hosted on solely on S3","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/gsg/S3-gsg-CommonUseScenarios.html","title":"Use Cases - S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"7a2b1017f16fb3e5ef49418e637aac95","text":"E-Commerce websites","correct":false},{"id":"0e40272fa3d5a16e33d87e3cbc4e1e47","text":"Dynamic websites","correct":false},{"id":"6c64eca998fc24821b4da679e88bb285","text":"Static websites","correct":true},{"id":"70ebe1a12fc1b6b0489f44de54de9fc3","text":"Streaming websites","correct":false}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true}]},{"id":"2c5901f2-c18a-456c-8a19-5d2da6952cec","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, this includes all aspects of capacity management, therefore it is an AWS responsibility to make sure that they never run out of storage. Replication to another AZ is also AWS's responsibility in an applicable storage tier - note that the question asks for AZ replication - not Regional Replication which would normally be the customer's responsibility to configure. AWS is also responsible for managing data corruption and resolving it if corruption is detected - however if it cannot fix the corruption, or if data is lost, AWS bears no responsibility for the loss - therefore it is a customer's responsibility to make sure there data is backup up as needed - either though versioning in S3, or through 3rd party tools.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/?nc=sn&loc=7","title":"S3 FAQ - Durability and Data Protection"}],"answers":[{"id":"18e8e0efaea5ce9a47da52086c745de7","text":"Making sure there is enough physical storage available for your data","correct":false},{"id":"96b64de5e30defc9bab2e6592e515b17","text":"Making sure that enough space has been provisioned for your data","correct":false},{"id":"caec507833650a0d1b82cc852d15ea1f","text":"Backing up your data","correct":true},{"id":"f5a4db96c8f945bbaddfca968bc66a00","text":"Replicating your data to another Availability Zone if redundancy is needed","correct":false},{"id":"f3cc93bd6eec33bc0d666a86175524cd","text":"Making sure your data is not corrupted","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true}]},{"id":"amvsqat1-leji-kqd6-yu62-421v3dktmzxn","domain":"tech","question":"You need to automate EC2 resource provisioning to meet demand. Which AWS service can help you accomplish this?","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to define thresholds, that when reached trigger the deployment of more EC2 resources. Load Balancers allow you to direct the flow of traffic and do not by themselves create other resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"6ff99ccd616e6ba3ca17de8fe56d016a","text":"EC2 container Service","correct":false},{"id":"e95e5a2a3cc8625bca3d71b817367e2d","text":"Elastic Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true}]},{"id":"024e0354-7a25-4a81-b42e-ce2af844e0e5","domain":"security","question":"Which service might you use to provide Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection to your applications running on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"ae4qnqr4-q2bm-f2dr-mvle-moqon5u5blu8","domain":"tech","question":"How can Auto Scaling help your resources handle changes in demand?","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to automatically add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify - these can include such things as at a specific time, or depending on how busy your application. Autoscaling cannot change the size of existing instances, nor can it add or change storage on an instance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"12545090042f77a088ab7bcaa6de4d72","text":"By increasing or decreasing the size of your EC2 instances based on conditions you specify","correct":false},{"id":"8d190956e7e4664d306007a2601517cd","text":"By increasing or decreasing the size of your storage based on conditions you specify","correct":false},{"id":"71b888b01492a657424f4f82588f0d28","text":"By adding or removing EC2 instances from your EC2 fleet based on conditions you specify","correct":true},{"id":"168c8ea8bcef87e54350e112c4067deb","text":"By adding or removing storage based on conditions you specify","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"cd73d505-c09a-44cb-a7fa-0ac6be0f5c99","domain":"tech","question":"Upon attempting to create an additional S3 bucket, you realize that you have reached your S3 bucket limit in your AWS account. You anticipate creating even more S3 buckets in the future for your photos and documents. Which of the following is the quickest solution?","explanation":"The key word here is 'quickest'. Granted, you can delete the S3 buckets of your choice, and you can try consolidating files into select buckets and deleting the emptied ones. But that could be quite a hassle to do, compared to simply requesting a service limit increase at the AWS Support Center. By default, you can create up to 100 buckets in an AWS account, and that is a limit that AWS does not override without officially requesting for a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"340d5ba6fcedb315c6adee97b1239f3f","text":"Consolidate files into half of the S3 buckets and delete the empty ones.","correct":false},{"id":"e7b93b6f7bea9c58f27912c7974c74d4","text":"Submit a service limit increase.","correct":true},{"id":"46bca3e00e40780aa04c28899f5bbe6b","text":"Simply create the S3 bucket; AWS will automatically override the bucket limit.","correct":false},{"id":"104e2902668d313ccfbc1bc78457e84d","text":"Delete the S3 buckets that you barely use.","correct":false}]},{"id":"e9686ec2-2edf-11ea-8a91-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS Security, Identity, and Compliance services?","explanation":"KMS makes it easy to create and manage cryptographic keys, Secrets Manager protects the secrets you use for access to applications and services, and Security Hub consolidates your view of your security and compliance status in the cloud. AWS Organizations, which is the odd one out, is strictly concerned with management; you can use it to consolidate multiple AWS accounts into an organization that you create and centrally manage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"d200c22f00ca54467dc4ad3823710388","text":"AWS Key Management Service (KMS)","correct":true},{"id":"03883d80013dc0b2b972eccd5b93b56f","text":"AWS Security Hub","correct":true},{"id":"7898cb92c418aeed6974ede9cb146462","text":"AWS Secrets Manager","correct":true},{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false}]},{"id":"sf55l98e-bpq0-sh7t-wkah-ex19vhdc9bie","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support services do all accounts receive as part of the AWS Support Basic tier?","explanation":"The AWS Support Basic tier is the free support given to all AWS Accounts. All accounts receive Billing Support, because every customer needs an avenue to lodge disputes, or make requests around their billing. 24x7 Support, Architectural Support, and access to a Technical Account Manager are all elements of paid plans.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ef823966f6d09ca49ae0117fbeb6f17","text":"Architectural Support","correct":false},{"id":"c7703baf6849325c6dd9df112e8b4b85","text":"Billing Support","correct":true},{"id":"4e88de53dbfa7fddf03f15ad5fd53eec","text":"Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"30c247eb11a68c65f4625c0a83e97cdb","text":"24/7 support via phone and chat","correct":false}]},{"id":"wfisjo0f-usp3-160k-im9l-di4ay4ny42e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service is specifically designed to assist you in processing large data sets?","explanation":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR) is a service that makes it easy to process large amounts of data efficiently. Redshift is a data warehousing solution. ElastiCache is used for caching data in memory for high speed read-access. EC2 is a general purpose compute service for hosting virtual servers. Whilst you could run big data processing tasks on EC2, it will be easier on EMR, which has been designed specifically for this purpose","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/emr/","title":"About EMR"}],"answers":[{"id":"50848259480914860b338e7baf94c29a","text":"ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"be94b3c024501e2d7e9e64f4e0d18af9","text":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR)","correct":true},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"d4c61d1c-2ada-4bc2-9cf9-2546f8d62025","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid S3 bucket names?","explanation":"The 'January-2020-sales-numbers' is the only S3 bucket name that is not valid; bucket names must not contain uppercase letters, and they must start with a lowercase letter or number. The other three responses are valid, since they do not violate bucket naming rules.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"9b55e7cfabcca3d69f5596c5122f46b2","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/january-2020-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"429e0b5ab4b0f9b9f14d8be62cecde68","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2020-january-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"5843ebf1fe3709048eb1d4ca8bdc00aa","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/012020-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"799de5bb8d3ce8dd91b7c8416efaa490","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/January-2020-sales-numbers","correct":false}]},{"id":"2o4xzter-rc6s-wz14-cd0x-5ymcmahyoj0q","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an EC2 instance on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, EC2 patching is a Shared Control - AWS is responsible for the underlying hardware, but you as the user is responsible for patching the OS and Applications running in your instance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"92d4ae83f773c1e79ec7ae29b20fa481","text":"Patching the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"b8a5da87a2cdeca59f9782e25182f574","text":"Patching the applications","correct":true},{"id":"ce74e3a1c22bccb58acc0062f43153bd","text":"Patching the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3e164c265c82649647e641e322d93aa7","text":"Patching the operating system","correct":true}]},{"id":"trwylx1o-zl9g-9de6-rxeg-gp4pakkifop1","domain":"tech","question":"The load on your application fluctuates by day of the week. Wednesdays have the most traffic; Saturdays have the least traffic. Which AWS service allows you to ensure you have the correct amount of compute capacity while also optimizing on a cost basis? ","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify. Auto-Scaling events can be scheduled to meet predictable changes in the load on your application.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"a2c64f657687c46ed9811761849051e4","text":"EC2 Container Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWS’s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"fde3bfdf-a9fa-4476-b785-b8de7b315aeb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following languages can be used to author CloudFormation templates?","explanation":"CloudFormation supports both JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) and YAML Ain't Markup Language (aka YAML) for authoring CloudFormation templates.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/working-with-templates-cfn-designer-json-editor.html","title":"Integrated JSON and YAML Editor"}],"answers":[{"id":"9463f87bbed1fcdacfb8d40e185ca2bc","text":"YAML","correct":true},{"id":"a7f5f35426b927411fc9231b56382173","text":"Python","correct":false},{"id":"2a52ba6e26e550c59e15affa051e478b","text":"CAMEL","correct":false},{"id":"0ecd11c1d7a287401d148a23bbd7a2f8","text":"JSON","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true}]},{"id":"zejpj051-p0tv-b1pt-hvqk-i5pz24d88v68","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service allows you to run code without having to worry about provisioning any underlying resources (such as virtual machines, databases etc.)","explanation":"Lambda is the AWS Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) offering that lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. Elastic Container Service (ECS) uses containers, but still requires management of the underlying servers to some extent. EC2 uses traditional servers, and does require all the other resources to be provisioned and setup. DynamoDB is specifically used for storing information in non-relational databases, and is unable to run code.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online — without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online — without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false},{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false},{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false},{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false}]},{"id":"c2f17cbb-c270-426b-9312-2e5b0ed2b32c","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following database migrations are classified as heterogenous?","explanation":"In heterogenous database migrations, the source and target databases tend to be different in schema structure, data type, and database code. So, to simplify migration from Oracle and Microsoft SQL Server to Amazon Aurora, AWS automatically converts the source database schema and most of the custom code to a format compatible with Aurora. By contrast, Amazon RDS includes Oracle Database as one of its database engines, and Aurora is MySQL-compatible, so a migration from Oracle to Amazon RDS for Oracle or MySQL to Aurora is straightforward and does not need a conversion.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon RDS"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"Amazon Aurora"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dms/","title":"AWS Database Migration"}],"answers":[{"id":"4c8e638aed3a82bf4024b088487c5ff7","text":"MySQL to Amazon Aurora","correct":false},{"id":"fe2b9abea260f2445909c9cb6930e5b4","text":"Microsoft SQL Server to Amazon Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"69923ac784b64e6a0719080837ad7d31","text":"Oracle to Amazon RDS for Oracle","correct":false},{"id":"8cfffb1f6f5bfb85dae8b92ae8b1a1fa","text":"Oracle to Amazon Aurora","correct":true}]}]}}}}
